

# **Muhammad Ibrahim Shoaib**

#### **Curriculum vitae**

#### **Summary**

Organized and detail-oriented, which allows me to effectively manage my time and prioritize my responsibilities. In addition to academic activities, I am also actively involved in extracurricular activities, always passionate to inspire young children, involving in research projects and leadership roles in various clubs and organizations. Also pursuing my passion regarding Computer Science through self-learning and opportunities provided by my college.

#### **Education**

Currently pursuing A-level second year (A2) in Beacon House College Programme

Institute	Curriculum	Results
Beaconhouse School System	O-levels	8A*, 1A, 1C
Beaconhouse College Programme	A-levels (AS 1st Year)	3As, 1B
Beaconhouse College Programme	A-levels (A2 2nd Year)	1A, 3Bs

### **Experience**

(Summer 2021-2022) President of Synergy Summer Camp

- Head of Management of the Summer Camp
- Also part of Science Department
  - Held experiments by hand to inspire children about the wonders of science in daily life.
  - Taught basic programming

(2018-2023) Acive part of The Debating Society

- Taking parts in different formats of speeches
- Also played part in conducting events inside and outside college

(2018-2023) Acive part of The Debating Society

- Taking parts in different formats of speeches
- Also played part in conducting events inside and outside college

(2022-2023) Intern at Crescent Textile Mills [IT Department]

- Fixing bugs in their software
- Creating their wesite
- Got the award for best intern of the year 2022

(2021-2023) Founder and CEO of Growth Xelerate

- A Social Media Marketing Company
- Helping people to boost their Social Media presence and introducing many bussinesses to the Digital World
- Also creating Websites for people and helping them rank on Google through SEO (Search Engine Optimisation) and BackLinking

#### **Skills**

Proficient in Python, also intermediate in Web Development

Fluent in English, Urdu and Punjabi

Strong communication and leadership abilities, as demonstrated through my Debating Career and Internship.

#### **Awards and Honors**

- Distinction in Biology (Highest marks in Pakistan) in CAIE O-levels 2020
- 2nd Position in British Parliamentary Debates 2023
- Part of management in managing BCP Debates 2022
  Management Review Parking and September 2022
- Managed Synergy Parlimentry Debates 2022President of Summer Camp 2021-2022
- Position in Beacon House Debating Competition
- Best intern of the year award 2022

## **Contact Info**

Email ibrahimshoaibx@gmail.com

Phone Number +923027256161

Current Address House # 652 Kayaban 2, Zeeshan Road, Khayaban Colony, Faisalabad